<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About me</string>
    <string name="com">You have sucessfully competed Reading</string>
    <string name="chara">Monkey D. Luffy</string>
    <string name="bio">The series focuses on Monkey D. Luffy—a young man made of rubber after
        unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit—who sets off on a journey from the East Blue Sea to
        find the deceased King of the Pirates Gol D. Roger\'s ultimate treasure known as the "One Piece",
        and takeover his prior title. In an effort to organize his own crew, the Straw Hat Pirates,[Jp 1]
        Luffy rescues and befriends a pirate hunter and swordsman named Roronoa Zoro, and they head off
        in search of the titular treasure. They are joined in their journey by Nami, a money-obsessed
        thief and navigator; Usopp, a sniper and compulsive liar; and Sanji, an amorous but chivalrous cook.
        They acquire a ship, the Going Merry[Jp 2]—later replaced by the Thousand Sunny[Jp 3]—and engage in
        confrontations with notorious pirates of the East Blue. As Luffy and his crew set out on their adventures,
        others join the crew later in the series, including Tony Tony Chopper, an anthropomorphized reindeer doctor;
        Nico Robin, an archaeologist and former Baroque Works assassin; Franky, a cyborg shipwright;
        Brook, a skeleton musician and swordsman; and Jimbei, a whale shark-type fish-man and former
        member of the Seven Warlords of the Sea who becomes their helmsman. Together, they encounter
        other pirates, bounty hunters, criminal organizations, revolutionaries, secret agents, different
        types of scientists, soldiers of the morally-ambiguous World Government, and various other friends
        and foes, as they sail the seas in pursuit of their dreams.</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="ragain">Read Again</string>
    <string name="your_nick_name">Your nick Name</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
</resources>